Lorraine Dukes Phone: (678) 661-9420

Email: <u>me@lorrainedukes.com</u> Portfolio: lorrainedukes.com

Cover Letter

To whom it may concern,

My name is Lorraine Dukes, I'm a Designer with over 12 years experience developing web and mobile solutions. My experience includes designing for companies such as Apple, AT&T, MovieTickets.com and many more.

I'm very interested in your current position. Please visit my portfolio website and learn more about me at: www.lorrainedukes.com

I look forward to speaking with you further about this opportunity. Thanks for your time and consideration!

Sincerely, Lorraine Dukes

Work Experience:

Freelance App Developer 1/2016-Present at <u>ZeroWire Tv</u>

Here I develop custom Android apps for the Android Tv market.

Development and Design Tools Used:

- Adobe Photoshop
- Android Studio

Freelance Wordpress Developer 10/2015- 1/2016 at <u>Begante</u>

Here I develop custom, WordPress solutions within PHP framework. I created stunning eye catching graphics to improve user interaction. Additionally I resolved functional issues within existing code to increase website performance.

Development and Design Tools Used:

- Adobe Photoshop
- PHP
- HTML5 CSS3
- Wordpress

Team Visual Designer 8/2012- 10/2015 at Apple

Responsibilities include crafting graphic elements, assets, and prototypes that are used to create internal apps, marketing emails and keynote presentations. I also developed an internal app called , "Chillout Radio" for use by employees to listen to music while working.

Other duties include QA testing new Apple products, services and apps in order to write case studies to provide insights and experiential feedback into the visual brand message.

Development and Design Tools Used:

- Adobe Photoshop (Graphics and Asset Development)
- HTML5 and CSS3 (Interactive Prototypes)
- Keynote (Training Presentations)
- Xcode (App Development)

Awards:

Recognized as top 5 employees of AppleCare organization in 2013.

User Experience Designer 8/2010- 8/2012 at AT&T

Worked with product teams to understand business needs, create interaction

designs and wireframes to translate them into stunning visual designs.

Engaged with development teams to understand platform capabilities, communicate design specifications, support agile development, and verify design implementations.

Development and Design Tools Used:

- Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator (Mockups and Asset Development)
- HTML5 and CSS3 (Interactive Prototypes)
- PowerPoint (Development Proposal Presentations)
- Microsoft Visio and iRise (Interaction Flow Charts)

Web Developer 8/2008-4/2010 at Schaffer Road Church of Christ

Responsible for conceptual development and execution of creative deliverables, including but not limited to collateral, print advertising, website content, etc.

Championed and communicated design best practices and guidelines to stakeholders throughout the organization.

Development and Design Tools Used:

- Adobe Photoshop (Graphics and Asset Development)
- HTML5 and CSS3 (Interactive Prototypes)
- PowerPoint (Training Presentations)

Graphic Designer 1/2008-8/2008 at Square One Art

Participated as a fully involved team member, coordinated projects with project managers, production specialists, and other team members to implement final printed products on a variety of material, including ceramics, fabrics, plastics, and wood.

Development and Design Tools Used:

- Adobe Photoshop (Graphic and Asset Design)
- Quark (Print layout)

Web Designer 3/02-12/02 at MovieTickets

Created theme microsite featuring games, polls and trivia for kids movie lovers. Developed interactive online games using Flash. Created stunning kid friendly graphics to foster brand loyalty from young users.

Development and Design Tools Used:

- Adobe Photoshop (Graphic and Asset Design)
- Flash
- HTML CSS

Founder/Director 9/2000 - Present at <u>Regen Creatives</u>

I run the show! I founded the agency in 2000. Here my team and I create, conceptualize and develop. I manage a small team of designers. I also perform administrative duties such as: billing, project management and customer service.

Education:

1997- High School Diploma - Plantation High School 2004 - Bachelors of Fine Arts –American Intercontinental University 2014- Certification in Web Design and Development - Kennesaw State University

Skill Set:

Agile Interaction Design App Design Wordpress Management
